# TAHA HUSSEIN ALREHANY

#### WEB DEVELOPER

### **SUMMARY**

Two years of experience developing websites in different web scripting languages (HTML, JavaScript and CSS)

Searching for a web developer job, to gain more in-depth skills and experience in project management, large websites, various tools and frameworks.

### CONTACT

#### Contact

- ♠ Nasr City, cairo, Egypt
- **L** +201150651396

#### Social

- in www.linkedin.com/in/taharehany
- f www.facebook.com/taha.rehany
- www.rehany.site
- © +201150651396

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Web Developer

Advertizer, Nasr City | 11/2018 - Present

- creating landing pages and websites for use in marketing campaigns.
- coding websites from scratch using various web tools such as (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript).
- use preprocessors to avoid wasting time and effort.
- · considerate to be the code is clean and concise.
- use different gadgets like computers, phones, and tablets to look at web pages responsive for design.
- web performance to make sure that website performs smoothly without any glitch and the amount of time it takes for site to load. such as optimizing images and minifying CSS and JavaScript.
- upload the site to the host and launch it.
- testing/debugging is an important part of any project to keep the bugs away.
- use browser developer tools.

#### Web Developer

freelance | 2018 - Present

worked in many freelance projects with many clients inside and outside Egypt for example:

- · a cars site for a customer in the UAE
- · moving furniture site.
- Advensco which is a startup software.

## PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

HTML	***	Pug js	***
CSS	****	Sass	****
Java Script	****	Type Script	****
Bootstrap	***	Angular	***
Wordpress	****	Photoshop	****

## PERSONAL SKILLS

Problem- ★★★★	Communication ★ ★ ★ ★
solving	Time ★★★★
Active listening ★ ★ ★ ★	management
Teamwork ★★★★	

## LINGUISTIC SKILLS

Skill group		Skill group	
Arabic	****	English	****

## **EDUCATION**

**2014 - 2018** B

### **Bachelor's Degree**

Al Azhar university graduated from faculty of Science with a good grade.